BROOKE MORTENSEN

801-556-6803



brookemorte@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/brookemortensen



github.com/brookemo



https://brookemo.github.io/

Front End Web Developer able to build a sophisticated website that not only looks great but works great too. Loves learning new technologies, and quick to pick up on them. Understands the importance of User Experience. A great team player and collaborator.

SKILLS

React.js, Node.js, Express, JavaScript, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3, MySQL, MongoDB, Github, Firebase, Bootstrap, Materialize, Media Queries, APIs, JSON, REST, AJAX, and the command line.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Bootcamp University of Utah

January 2018 - July 2018
A university accredited intensive bootcamp dedicated to building web applications from start to finish.

WORK HISTORY

Assistant & Wordpress Editor Single Dad Laughing LLC

September 2017 - February 2018 I edited and compiled image in Wordpress, managed the blogger's schedule, and ran his errands.

Lead Spa Concierge The Grand America Hotel

October 2015 - December 2017
I would deal with customer conflict
resolution and delivered Certified
Forbes 5 Star Service.

Receptionist

July 2014 - October 2015
I answered phones, wrote out breif summaries, filed paperwork and prepared meetings rooms.

APPLICATIONS BUILT

STARWARSPLANETS.COM FULL STACK DEVELOPER

- A web application that allows users to easily comb through and see which planets in the Star Wars universe appear in different movies, and give more information on them.
- I used Javascript, JSON, jQuery, HTML, CSS, and extensive media queries.

https://www.starwarsplanets.com/

https://github.com/BrookeMo/StarWarsPlanets

BRYNNANDKADEN.TK

FULL STACK DEVELOPER & DESIGNER

- · A wedding RSVP website where guests can sign up to be sent an invitation, and then once invitations are sent, can use to RSVP to the ceremony or reception.
- I used Sketch to design, and Firebase, AJAX calls, Javascript, JSON, jQuery, HTML, CSS, and extensive media queries.

http://www.brynnandkaden.tk/

https://github.com/BrookeMo/brynnandkaden

ACCESSIBLE TRAVEL

FRONTEND DEVELOPER & DESIGNER

- A web application to give safe, sensory friendly, and certified travel options for parents and individuals on the spectrum.
- I was also responsible for the full development of User Authentication. I used React.js, node.js, Javascript, jQuery, JSON, Materialize, CSS, HTML, and Firebase.

https://accessibletravel.herokuapp.com/

https://github.com/BrookeMo/AccessibleTravel

MAMMA MIA MEMORY GAME

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

- · A fun and easy memory game with characters from Mamma Mia.
- · I used React.js, node.js, HTML, CSS, Javascript, and jQuery.

https://brookemo.github.io/clickygame/

https://github.com/BrookeMo/clickygame